

PERSONAL PROFILE

A well experienced proffesional with proven creativity and innovative ideas. Can handle multitasking well and always dedicated on maintaining high standards with regards to his work. With management ability, a team player and welcomes new challenges.

SPECIALIZATIONS

- Themed Cakes and pastries
- Handmade figures using:
 - Chocolate
 - -marzipan and Pastillage
 - -sugars
 - -fruits and vegetables
- Pettipours

CONTACTS



chefartistbertes@gmail.com



in henrybertes



Daddydudes



+63 9182311880

9335697139

HENRY B.BERTES **EXECUTIVE PASTRY CHEF**

JOB EXPERIENCE

Disney Cruise line - Pastry chef -2010 - 2020

- monitors and enforces all culinary and operating procedures and provides feedback to the management.
- maintains a clean and safe environment as per USPH sanitation requirements.
- Supervises and ensures smooth daily operation.
- Provides culinary demonstration
- Provide assistance to the executive chef if required.
- Practices a good working attitude and always displays positivity.

Princess cruiseline - Chief Pastry chef -2014 - 2016

M/S Minerva Cruiseship - Pastry chef - 2009

M/S Amadea Cruiseship - Pastry chef - 2007 - 2008

Moka Cafe - Abu Dhabi, UAE

- 2003-2007 - Head Pastry chef

Millenium Airport Hotel - Dubai, UAE

- Pastry demi chef - 1999-2003

Opera Cafe - Doha Qatar

-1997 - 1999 - Cake Decorator

Westin Philippine Plaza - Pastry cook - 1995 - 1997

EDUCATION

Hotel and Restaurant management

- Graduate

- University of Manila

Certification

- Ship Cook Training/ NCIII Tesda Philippines
- Level 1 award food safety awareness
- Modecor Italiana SPA Cake decoration
- BST, Elementary First Aid, and personal safety
- Personal Survival Technique
- Crowd management
- Elementary First Aid Training Transition to Disney Leadership
- U.S.P.H. Training